<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>SINDHI MATRIMONIALS</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>24, Bride, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Hindu: Sindhi, Kota, Banking/ Insurance</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=04d631722b86b6fe326ea650d10c3f50i2776870&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> We are looking. for a match for our daughter Shweta.
Shweta is a sensitive, very loving and understanding girl with traditional values and high sense of responsibility. At the same time she is successfully pursuing her career as a Research Analyst. We see her as right blend of the traditional and th</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>35, Groom, 5&apos; 9&quot; , Hindu: Sindhi, , Others</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=e245213de42e047f0ac16220ca574b02i2926976&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> simple, down to. earth, caring, respectful, ambitious, looking for better half. like her to be beautiful, understanding and adjusting. promise to love and respect for the rest of my life. so god help me.  Looking for: looking for a genuine person who ishumble, smart, intelligent, beautiful knows how </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>30, Bride, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Hindu: Sindhi, Nagpur, Teaching/ Education/ Languages</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=3246f71d57be50dd919dbd6641330bbci87497&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I AM LECTURER., . SLIM, FAIR, ..motto of life:live let live. I would like to settle in NAGPUR. My Hobbies are LISTENING MUSIC, READING etc....  Looking for: EDUCATED, WELL-BEHAVED, CARING, A TRUE GENTLEMAN.preference:to nagpur</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>33, Groom, 5&apos; 9&quot; , Hindu: Sindhi, , Entrepreneur/ Businessmen</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=8f2602a42cc871abba2e18ff7c54a095i1443901&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I am a. very hardworking person and i live with my elder brother and his family here in Curacao, Netherland Antillies. I would like someone special who would love to live within a fun loving family. I have 2 elder brothers,  both married and both are working and living abroad. My late father was a ma</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>28, Bride, 5&apos; 4&quot; , Hindu: Sindhi, Bangalore, Fashion</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=455dc87e22bcfc33806079d11db17f42i2949430&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Hi... i am. a simple, fun loving honest n loyal person, im veri straight forward n a firm believer in God... i hate people with attitude, im lukin for sum1 who is sensible, n trustworthy. i believe in long term relationships.  Looking for: sum1 who is sensible, simple n down to earth, with a gud s</description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>