<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>SIKH MATRIMAONIALS</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>24, Bride, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Sikh: Jat, , IT Hardware/ Telecom</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=b20b9c7863c2009932ef768fa5405a52i2937403&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> She is born. and grown up in Germany and living with us - parents. 
Even she is born in Germany, she is an Indian culture and tradition oriented girl and looking for a good, loving Punjabi Sikh with a nice family. 
She can speak and write German and English. Understand and speak in Punjabi and Hind</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>27, Groom, 5&apos; 11&quot;, Sikh: Ramgarhia, Delhi, IT Software</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=503fec1f4715f1181bde422abc7bb112i2932325&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Simple down to. earth kind of a person, finds happiness in small things. and love to be genuine. One younger brother, He is a student of Science doing B.Sc. A very well settled family in Jabalpur (M.P.). Having one younger brother, Mom and Dad. Mom is a house wife and Dad is into business. It is my l</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>30, Bride, 5&apos; 3&quot; , Sikh: Ramgarhia, Delhi, Cust. Service/ Operations</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=16031e130a23fca5f7f98944614a5129i2933520&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I am looking. for suitable alliance / Life Partner for my sister, we are well establish family settle in New Delhi. We are three brother and sister and she being the youngest in the family.  </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>24, Groom, 5&apos; 10&quot;, Sikh: Khatri, , Student</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=12b9079e0a28cc42943eb445b5224a1ci888704&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> hye this is. monti i live in london persuing DTI course from middlesex college which is located in oxford circus .my whole family live in INDIA i do work in gatwick airport doing dti course affiliate to atlantic airlines. we are three brothers elder brother is a doctor in india mid elder brother </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>25, Bride, 5&apos; 4&quot; , Sikh: Jat, Delhi, Others</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=ab666bbb82c06764f06a47e03e0857dci1806515&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> She is smart, . confident, caring and fun- loving gal with a blend of traditional and modern values. With a good sense of humor and modern outlook yet family -oriented.
Father : Retired Engineer from Gov. Sector
Mother : Home Maker
Elder Brother(1st): Working as as Sales Manager. Married    </description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>