<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>RAJASTHANI MATRIMONIALS</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>25, Bride, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Hindu: Maheshwari, Raipur, Architecture/ Interior Design</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=80e7c4bdf0725cc8287a7bc2af08d08fi2926480&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> my self fun. loving gul.who lives in her own rules d regulation.working as an interior designer d seeking some gud business oppurtunity .who wanna a life partner who is well educated, smart, d very close to his family.  Looking for: i wanna a guy.who lives his life fulliest.he shud be gud educated, sma</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>34, Groom, 5&apos; 7&quot; , Hindu: Maheshwari, Bhilwara, Accounts/ Tax/ CS/ Audit</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=c1080e5c6f65e90f35e94d54340d509ei2798593&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Virendra is self. promoted person, he belives in present . He is Chartered Accountant and his life style thinking is modern . He is practiceing CA now.  Looking for: She must be educated, intelligent, charming. She is adjustable,  follow indian traditional culture . </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>23, Bride, 5&apos; 0&quot; , Hindu: Marwari, Mumbai, Teaching/ Education/ Languages</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=6ee621323593463ffb8d7ee65bd9d1bai2749823&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I am very. homely girl and very caring.very responsible person.i love teaching.I have a family of 4.i am elder and younger brother is working wid a foreign company and mom dad.i love my family a lot.i luv dancing.  Looking for: i want my life partner 2 atleast be a graduate who allows me 2 work afte</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>34, Groom, 5&apos; 9&quot; , Hindu: Marwari, Kolkata, Entrepreneur/ Businessmen</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=3175d9d194d6728e5a77e673a64393cai2888551&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> my son is. very simple fun loving guy he has no bad habits like drinking smoking and has very simple life style and love to travel i have one elder brother who work sepretly and one elder sister who is housewife my father in is retierd and mother is housewife Looking for: she should be very simple n</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>31, Bride, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Hindu: Vaishnav, Hyderabad, Student</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=91a0b3e5f092018788755f944b47e8a6i2701935&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Well I am. a caring, easy going, honest, funloving and an adjusting person by nature. My hobbies are reading, listening to music, cooking and painting. 

I am fairly liberal yet traditional and believe in living life to the fullest and facing every challenge with a smile and a positive attitude. 
</description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>