<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>BENGALI MATRIMONIAL</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>34, Bride, 4&apos; 11&quot;, Hindu: Kayastha, Kolkata, Teaching/ Education/ Languages</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=c89ff236d59301c0ef258ed9b4b71e5ci1924025&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I am a. teacher working in a reputed Eng-medium school in Kolkata. I am M.A.(J.U.) B.ed (1st class;C.U.), computer-literate, quiet, good-looking, practical, homely belong to a good family background Hobbies: Painting, reading, listening to music, gardening. Two younger sisters only. Both studying i</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>28, Groom, 5&apos; 6&quot; , Hindu: Kayastha, Kolkata, Others</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=3ff0d706a594c0dc049c7bc859d83b0fi2912914&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Hi.I am Subhadeep.working. in Merchant Navy as a 2nd Officer (due for promotion to Chief Officer shortly).I am basically a simple guy who loves to hang out with friends once in a while and go for movies.Am not a party kind of person at all.Love music and enjoy driving a lot. One sister got married la</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>32, Bride, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Christian: Catholic, Kolkata, Teaching/ Education/ Languages</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=1c4d9aa14cfed21c2916132e0d50c7d2i2734831&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Hi ! I. am a simple, funloving and a very friendly person.I have a very liberal outlook to life but have been brought up with strong values.I value relationships and find joy in the simple pleasures of life..!  Looking for: I am looking for someone who is presentable, qualified and well established.It</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>40, Groom, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin, Lucknow, Medical/ Healthcare</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=16c519d077c186f3b3dad5d1ab178706i2816397&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Im a self. employed med. professional with a dream to wipe off tears from others faces. I live with my Ma younger brother-a Ph.D. scholar. Im also working as a lecturer in Eram Medical college. I can speak write Bangla, Hindi, English sanskrit with little Urdu. I can understand little French</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>29, Bride, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Hindu: Kayastha, Delhi, Architecture/ Interior Design</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=b5eb51b32dd22ad9b1f356af00c77e3di2718958&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Hi i am. Anjana. I am frdly, simple, fun luving girl:) wants to keep love alive for lifetime as is the most precious thing in our life. i value frdship a lot, and respect all relationships . i luv travelling, music most essential thing in my life:)(learning guitar ), luv to watch movies, hate saas ba</description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>