<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>TELUGU MATRIMONIALS</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>28, Bride, 5&apos; 1&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Vaidiki, Mumbai, Cust. Service/ Operations</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=3f91088da4b3284199d88899cadb707fi2901498&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Hi, Im simple, . easy going, talkative ambitious. I am brought up at many places due to my fathers transferable job. I can speak telugu, english, hindi and gujarati. I am brought up in a family where traditions matter however as the time passed they are moderate now. I am working for Countrywide f</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>47, Groom, 6&apos; 0&quot; , Hindu: Kamma, Coimbatore, Accounts/ Tax/ CS/ Audit</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=c66dea945548da0eef516d409eccea48i404243&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I am a. simple person. Look younger than my age suggets.Hail basically from agri. family. Have a brother and two sisters - all are married. Looking for a person who can make our lives more meaningful  </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>30, Bride, 5&apos; 6&quot; , Hindu: Kayastha, Pune, Legal/ Law</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=34c46d81b79e126a80e2372e476f5a40i207645&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> She is tall, . slim, smart, lovable, charming, soft spoken, simple, down to earth, Religious , kind hearted, with good family values and culture,  has done BSL LLB . Working and adaptable to situations 

We are from Andhra, Kamma but settled in Maharshtra from generations. Father retd. Class I offic</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>28, Groom, 6&apos; 0&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin 6000 Niyogi, USA - Georgia, IT Software</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=6847f3605221f4ed7dcb7c7cd34c4b92i2742047&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Kiran is our. youngest son. He is broad minded, fun loving, caring, outgoing, spiritual, 6 feet tall with an impressive personality, healthy, handsome, non-smoking, non-alcoholic, pure vegetarian and well settled with a mix of eastern and western cultures. He is presently working as a Software Engine</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>23, Bride, 5&apos; 1&quot; , Hindu: Arya Vysya, Hyderabad, Others</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=e53898ed0cd2ecf80619bac7ab4b96dai1152194&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I AM. BRAD MINDED I ALSO LOOKING for SO STEBILISED, 
 S/ W  IT JOB HOLDER, COOL SOFT GUY. BUT Iam AGREE PREFERD TO ONLY  HOUSE WIFE. Iam A NICE FOOD MAKING 
 EXPERT. GUMMADAVELLY  DHANALAXMI ELDER SISTER, SOFTWARE ENGINEER IN hitec city  CTS .she got a baby. KANDIBANDA GURUMURTHY. </description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>