<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>PUNJABI MATRIMONIALS</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>24, Bride, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Sikh: Jat, , IT Hardware/ Telecom</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=b20b9c7863c2009932ef768fa5405a52i2937403&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> She is born. and grown up in Germany and living with us - parents. 
Even she is born in Germany, she is an Indian culture and tradition oriented girl and looking for a good, loving Punjabi Sikh with a nice family. 
She can speak and write German and English. Understand and speak in Punjabi and Hind</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>22, Groom, 5&apos; 11&quot;, Muslim: Sunni, , Govt. Services</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=ef9034ddb94ca058d1be69977fe17671i2944106&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> hi my name. is liyas mohammad. i am from punjab city phillaur/ but i am living with family on uk permanent/ but my big brother living on punjab i looking for good girl .my age 22 my 2 brother 1 leve with me uk.1 on india and marrid big brother. my 1 sister leve with me uk marrid on itlya my father is </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>25, Bride, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Hindu: Khatri, Gurgaon, Fashion</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=cdd7f142414c86f3d1a354dd0775084ei2930356&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Anu (my sister), . currently working as a Merchandiser in MNC at Gurgaon. She is an affectionate girl who values the interpersonal and family relations. Apart from being Genuine and simple by nature, she is quite sincere and ambitious for her career aspects. Being emotional, she deserves a partner who</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>49, Groom, 5&apos; 7&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin, Hyderabad, Accounts/ Tax/ CS/ Audit</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=2d4996b261517fa69235e5b3b2d368fdi563296&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> This post is. for my brother who is chartered accountant/ LLB.He is simple, shy and very caring loving person.......he has very good sense of humor and is god fearing person.He is hard working and enjoys good music looking for a suitable partner for life.We lost our father in 21 and our mom in Septe</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>30, Bride, 5&apos; 1&quot; , Hindu: Arora, Delhi, Legal/ Law</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=7399c72f3eb5b05752369822cabb1dafi2369952&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> My daughter is. caring, affectionate, hardworking, down to earth, beautiful and slim. She is practicing as a advocate in Delhi Courts.We believe in traditional as well as modern values. We are looking for professionally qualified boy.  Looking for: He should be professionally qualified cultured. </description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>