<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>INDIAN MATRIMONIALS</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>26, Bride, 5&apos; 0&quot; , Hindu: Mali, Baroda, Medical/ Healthcare</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=cdf3e51d683590072de3d3bd14da903fi2913340&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> good looking wellcultured. from rich family and highly qualified. Occupation laboratory related. life style  Looking for: highly qualified well cultured and good family background.</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>32, Groom, 5&apos; 5&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Viswa, Mumbai, R&amp;D/ Engineering Design</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=45886f1cac24e61e18414257eb8c3083i2827659&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> hi thanks for. looking at my profile. currently am a researcher in a US university. i am just looking here for my soul mate who is simple, well educated and with good understanding.  Looking for: should be well educated, simple and with good understanding</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>30, Bride, 5&apos; 4&quot; , Hindu: Mali, Mumbai, Medical/ Healthcare</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=33ce91538b9d1c4a73256fce1cc51da8i1639071&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> i have done. MBBS, DCH. i am a simple person who takes life as it comes. i want my partner should be a simple person who will understand me. 
  I like reading, writing, traveling, cooking.I like to spend time with my family.
   
my father is a retired engineer.mother is a housewife.elder sister i</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>22, Groom, 5&apos; 11&quot;, Muslim: Sunni, , Govt. Services</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=ef9034ddb94ca058d1be69977fe17671i2944106&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> hi my name. is liyas mohammad. i am from punjab city phillaur/ but i am living with family on uk permanent/ but my big brother living on punjab i looking for good girl .my age 22 my 2 brother 1 leve with me uk.1 on india and marrid big brother. my 1 sister leve with me uk marrid on itlya my father is </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>28, Bride, 5&apos; 1&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Vaidiki, Mumbai, Cust. Service/ Operations</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=3f91088da4b3284199d88899cadb707fi2901498&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Hi, Im simple, . easy going, talkative ambitious. I am brought up at many places due to my fathers transferable job. I can speak telugu, english, hindi and gujarati. I am brought up in a family where traditions matter however as the time passed they are moderate now. I am working for Countrywide f</description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>