<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>HINDU MATRIMONIALS</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>26, Bride, 5&apos; 0&quot; , Hindu: Mali, Baroda, Medical/ Healthcare</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=cdf3e51d683590072de3d3bd14da903fi2913340&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> good looking wellcultured. from rich family and highly qualified. Occupation laboratory related. life style  Looking for: highly qualified well cultured and good family background.</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>32, Groom, 5&apos; 5&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Viswa, Mumbai, R&amp;D/ Engineering Design</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=45886f1cac24e61e18414257eb8c3083i2827659&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> hi thanks for. looking at my profile. currently am a researcher in a US university. i am just looking here for my soul mate who is simple, well educated and with good understanding.  Looking for: should be well educated, simple and with good understanding</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>26, Bride, 5&apos; 4&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin, USA - California, Legal/ Law</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=b1033497f356870744be7a1da967a4adi2933956&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Completed her B.A.. degree in Political Science and just finished her M.A. in Criminal Justice. She wants to pursue Law. She is 26 years of age (date of birth: Feb. 26, 1981, Anuradha Nakshatra, Kashyapa Gotra). She is 54 tall and slim and of fair complexion. She is kind hearted and very considerat</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>28, Groom, 5&apos; 9&quot; , Hindu: Kayastha, Pune, IT Software</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=a863679634a12189e71cd8ff566f1d12i1821007&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Rahul is a. handsome and understanding guy. He is working with Indias largest software company as an IT Analyst. He is well educated and pursued M.Tech. from IIT Delhi. He goes abroad very often for long as well as short durations therefore looking for an accommodative partner who can accompany him </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>26, Bride, 5&apos; 5&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Iyer, , Home Maker</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=b603bec8d61376907eb439844cd37460i2944231&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Beautiful, talented outgoing
Bachelors. Masters degree from Australia
Presently living with Parents wishes to settle down with a compatible person preferably with a similar background Married brother settled in the US.
Is a senior manager with a top consultancy firm in the US Father is a avi</description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>