<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>TAMIL MATRIMONIALS</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>35, Bride, 5&apos; 7&quot; , Hindu: Others, Chennai, Logistics/ Purchase/ SCM</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=fea55be40da2d7ddca8a2d11b64433a6i2913567&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Hi! I am. a confident and practical, down to earth person who believes in having a fair balance between career and family..I hope to have a business of my own in the future. I am ideally looking for a honest and good person with integrity.
I am currently visiting NY, USA but am not a paid member so </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>25, Groom, 5&apos; 9&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Iyer, Tamil Nadu, Others</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=f73cc18c38990ae0c52f84686d088337i2940037&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> hello this is. ram basically i am a hard working guy, i am quite fat, we are tanjore brahmins with good family backgound, my family consist of mother sister only, my hobbies is to listening to music pet care cooking.i am working in hyundai motor india as a JE monthly income is 25, needs a fair </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>30, Bride, 5&apos; 4&quot; , Hindu: Pillai, Madurai, IT Software</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=d4239b9efeeba70777bf2345b32797a8i2146308&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Hi  thanks. for stopping by my profile

Just a quick glimpse about me… Im neither an introvert nor an extrovert but a mix of both. I just admire nature, innocence of a child, flowers, drizzling,  ……..and so on. I love music and dance. And there are many more to pen down, but I would like to share</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>33, Groom, 6&apos; 0&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Iyer, Bangalore, IT Software</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=920c32dfae6c0e8e8353aa8b544f961fi2730713&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> My son Suresh. was in USA from 1997 up to Nov 26. He is now working in Banglore with a multinational. Divorced has no children. 

Parents live in Pune. 

One brother lives in USA with wife and child.
Suresh wants to marry a career focused, friendly family loving girl. Suresh is interested in t</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>31, Bride, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Iyer, Kolkata, Fashion</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=dbe88532a6a3e54b9d9206e67f8f3331i2091971&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> palakkad brahmin vadama. moola2, 5-2, slim, fair, B.Com, NIFT (N.Delhi) own studio in kolkata, father retd.Ex. Director (Eng), 2 brothers both Engineers, elder sister NID (visual comm.), one brother and sister married. not very religious but to spiritualism, intellectual persuits in the field of r</description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>