<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>CANADA MATRIMONIALS</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>47, Bride, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Madhwa, , Others</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=8071e7dfb1716090aba0fe7a452250b2i2927163&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> A very down. to earth loving person who enjoys western music, English movies, travelling, crossword puzzles, sudoku etc. Looking for a person who is honest, trustworthy, sincere, loving and who is commited to marriage.  </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>24, Groom, 5&apos; 9&quot; , Hindu: Pillai, , Student</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=88ac5a2ec920e6cfebc9d77a34390663i2949094&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> am simple in. nature ... fun loving n a open minded person .. social type....respectful to others ... having fun alwayz n mak others happy .. so sensitive ... n i am looking for a girl who is zealous wid ma family. I have an younger bro doing his Bachelors in Engg. My father is doing his business n </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>25, Bride, 5&apos; 3&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin, , Student</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=17b88cd5bb419be43304a275a92f6abfi691002&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> After a years. study at grad school in the US, my daughter is presently in Canada to pursue MSc and then plans for a Ph.D as well. She has already done her Masters in Zoology from M.S.University of Baroda, and then an Advanced Diploma in Bioinformatics from University of Pune. No siblings I, the gir</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>26, Groom, 6&apos; 0&quot; , Muslim: Sunni, , Architecture/ Interior Design</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=0663eea404ef97e3703c27f7c73a34f0i2638205&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> every one. well sattled.! they are retired now..! Looking for: Belong to easy going, down to earth family. simple, reasonably intelligent. Partner should be intelligent and loyal, deep understanding.</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>29, Bride, 5&apos; 7&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Audichya, , Corporate Commn./ PR</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=df90af6286d97c7f34a32e156808acf2i2949642&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I am a. happy person. Iam well settled in canada. I am hard working. I like to listen to music. I am fair in complexion  Looking for: Be truthful loving</description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>