<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>MUSLIM MATRIMONIALS</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>25, Bride, 5&apos; 6&quot; , Muslim: Sunni, Lucknow, Others</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=c0aebb061c06c8e1f22f46e7b73c7785i2914749&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Well educated, homely, . very beautiful, simple, cultured girl from respectable sayyed family.
innocent divorcee. done her bachelors in arts from lucknow. Father in bank service, mother house wife. One younger brother. One young brother completing C.A. Father is a Senior Manager in U.P. Cooperative B</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>22, Groom, 5&apos; 11&quot;, Muslim: Sunni, , Govt. Services</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=ef9034ddb94ca058d1be69977fe17671i2944106&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> hi my name. is liyas mohammad. i am from punjab city phillaur/ but i am living with family on uk permanent/ but my big brother living on punjab i looking for good girl .my age 22 my 2 brother 1 leve with me uk.1 on india and marrid big brother. my 1 sister leve with me uk marrid on itlya my father is </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>40, Bride, 5&apos; 6&quot; , Muslim: Sunni, Bhopal, Airlines/ Reservations/ Travel</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=29a34eaae80fc4b1825faee18ac2d064i557074&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I am 39. yr old divorcee.Ht 56, fair, beautiful with sharp features. I have done MA in English Literature and in Arabic, E-Commerce, Multi-Media and IATA. I am a homely person. My hobbies include cooking and computers. I have a 18 yr old daughter, who lives with her maternal grand parents. We are </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>29, Groom, 5&apos; 5&quot; , Muslim: Sunni, , Advtg/ Media/ Mktg/ MR</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=016d4201d0a4673489d3b36d8979b4a5i2521455&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Hi, I am. IYAS. From Kerala, Working Dubai in a privet company.i will settled to india soon. I am a simple and broad minded man...MY PARTNER TO BE VERY NEAREST AND DEAREST TO ME, like a close friend....  Looking for: broadminded, undrestanding...etc.</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>28, Bride, 5&apos; 1&quot; , Muslim: Sunni, Madhya Pradesh, Others</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=497e739b2296291200e590066f657fabi2885806&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> ALLAH fearing, having. positive attitude and well versed in cooking, knitting, crafting and every other household work.  Looking for: Practicing muslim values based on the teachings of Quran and Sunnah, with positive attitude towards life bearing high moral and social values. Committed to relations</description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>