<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>GUJARATI MATRIMONIALS</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>26, Bride, 5&apos; 0&quot; , Hindu: Mali, Baroda, Medical/ Healthcare</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=cdf3e51d683590072de3d3bd14da903fi2913340&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> good looking wellcultured. from rich family and highly qualified. Occupation laboratory related. life style  Looking for: highly qualified well cultured and good family background.</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>26, Groom, 6&apos; 4&quot; , Hindu: Lohana, Kandla, Banking/ Insurance</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=885a80e9ee73c870ca788c0bd34778a3i1922019&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> i am an. ambitious and at the same time family oriented person with a wonderful and supportive family I always put in my best to achieve my goal and belive in; 
A crucial point comes in everyone life where he/ she wants to feel a whole
person. I believe marriage is a long term commitment and for a s</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>36, Bride, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Hindu: Vaishnav, Mumbai, IT Software</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=d08e0146381ddc0b0f6e2c52ed165d35i111690&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I like Indian. dancing,  Singing. Watching movies, Hindi English Both. I am a very talkative, Frank ,  straightforward, jovial person who can mix around make friends fast, disciplined but also fun loving . I am a pure Vegetarian, Indian looking out for a well educated, smart, jovial, vegetarian, </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>25, Groom, 5&apos; 9&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Audichya, Ahmedabad, IT Software</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=751670fd2a1837a6f6b17a6e1e5bea8ei1449608&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> To brief up..... I completed my college from Bangalore and started with my professional career from Bangalore itself. Its been around 2 half years since I relocated to Ahmedabad and working here as Software QA Engineer.

My interest goes with automobiles, studying techno trends, photography, musi</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>27, Bride, 5&apos; 3&quot; , Hindu: Patel Leva, Gujarat, Others</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=2f3e1addcc3945560c68ba44c13c89b9i2913618&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> she is gujrati. leva patel girl very good looking, simple and hard working girl, able to face any kind of situation. father is engineer and mom is house wife.  </description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>