<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>KERALA MATRIMONIALS</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>29, Bride, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Christian: Pentecost, USA - New York, Legal/ Law</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=7f2a72f7cb326e733525c5f966fcdd98i1761814&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I consider myself. to be a sweet, loving, and compassionate person. My interests are music, art, traveling/ sightseeing, working out, God and Church and various other things. I every so often would love to watch a movie. I love singing and playing the piano. I am looking for a match who complements </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>29, Groom, 5&apos; 5&quot; , Muslim: Sunni, , Advtg/ Media/ Mktg/ MR</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=016d4201d0a4673489d3b36d8979b4a5i2521455&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Hi, I am. IYAS. From Kerala, Working Dubai in a privet company.i will settled to india soon. I am a simple and broad minded man...MY PARTNER TO BE VERY NEAREST AND DEAREST TO ME, like a close friend....  Looking for: broadminded, undrestanding...etc.</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>26, Bride, 5&apos; 4&quot; , Hindu: Ezhava, Kochi, Airlines/ Reservations/ Travel</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=25481a36c634b065a6d7906b97be6270i1989482&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> hi,  i. am a airhostess working for an international airline which an sub airline for the countrys national carrier.i am based in kochin right now. i am a getgoer person.99% independant.i belong to an nuclear family,  father retried fm defence ad mom an home maker. have brother who is in final year o</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>30, Groom, 5&apos; 10&quot;, Hindu: Ezhava, Thiruvananthapuram, Others</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=f3bb614aea5ed5697c231cf357941b94i2918065&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I am a. technetion . working in saudiarebia my father ezhava mother nair my life is village atmospher i have one syster she was marridge my father no mor I have 8 years old he died I am looking for a educated simple lovable character and well family statous not a money statous  Looking for: simpl</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>26, Bride, 5&apos; 4&quot; , Christian: Catholic, , Medical/ Healthcare</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=8b9a4f80b689f2fce679d747c7b52fb5i2350066&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I am working. in MOH SA as a staff nurse. Would like to marry from knanaya catholic. Looking for Graduate level educated working either in Kerala Govt. sector or boys in middle east countries with family visa status or in UK, Europe, USA or Australia. Brother married, working KWA in Palai Father Far</description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>