<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>LOOKING FOR NRI BRIDES</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>26, Bride, 5&apos; 5&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Iyer, , Home Maker</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=b603bec8d61376907eb439844cd37460i2944231&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Beautiful, talented outgoing
Bachelors. Masters degree from Australia
Presently living with Parents wishes to settle down with a compatible person preferably with a similar background Married brother settled in the US.
Is a senior manager with a top consultancy firm in the US Father is a avi</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>44, Bride, 5&apos; 6&quot; , Hindu: Others, USA - New Jersey, Advtg/ Media/ Mktg/ MR</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=8c273d52d2586788ce5d94a409194f85i2948250&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I AM JUST. COMMING USA PRESENT WE ARE STAYING WITH MY BROTHER, AT ABSECON AND MY OTHER BROTHER AT CHICAGI IL,   Looking for: Very Co-Operative, Joint Family Nature, </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>53, Bride, 5&apos; 0&quot; , Hindu: Vaishnav Vanik, USA - New Jersey, Banking/ Insurance</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=6ba28c0be0ae5910a097c81ee516f117i2109676&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I am simple. person. 
My Outdoor Activities:
Besides going to Gym (trade mill swimming toning muscles spa),  I regularly do Yoga and Meditation. I enjoy hiking, nature walk, feeding birds, sight seeing (Swiss, Hawaii, Bahamas.), watching movies (comedy, sentimental) and Broadway shows.
And Indoor </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>36, Bride, 5&apos; 3&quot; , Hindu: Patel, USA - New Jersey, Medical/ Healthcare</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=faab775f0ad60b810cc1e70491f28a9ai1962846&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I would describe. myself as warm-hearted, cheerful, independent, spiritual, sensible, spontaneous, freedom loving and simple person but I can also be fun given the appropriate situation and company. 

I am looking for a life partner who shares common beliefs, values, views, goals and will be comple</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>39, Bride, 5&apos; 4&quot; , Hindu: Others, USA - New York, Beauty, Health &amp; Fitness Professional</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=c0ee041d302a11f34fe3a97107882a97i2948040&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> very well balanced, . health conscious, fair, slim simple but very professional willing settle down with right person.  Looking for: Well educated, well settled who is willing to settled down has family values with modern approach towards life.</description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>