<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>LOOKING FOR A COSMOPOLITAN LIFE PARTNER?????????</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>26, Bride, 5&apos; 0&quot; , Hindu: Mali, Baroda, Medical/ Healthcare</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=cdf3e51d683590072de3d3bd14da903fi2913340&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> good looking wellcultured. from rich family and highly qualified. Occupation laboratory related. life style  Looking for: highly qualified well cultured and good family background.</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>49, Groom, 5&apos; 7&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin, Hyderabad, Accounts/ Tax/ CS/ Audit</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=2d4996b261517fa69235e5b3b2d368fdi563296&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> This post is. for my brother who is chartered accountant/ LLB.He is simple, shy and very caring loving person.......he has very good sense of humor and is god fearing person.He is hard working and enjoys good music looking for a suitable partner for life.We lost our father in 21 and our mom in Septe</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>35, Bride, 5&apos; 7&quot; , Hindu: Others, Chennai, Logistics/ Purchase/ SCM</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=fea55be40da2d7ddca8a2d11b64433a6i2913567&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Hi! I am. a confident and practical, down to earth person who believes in having a fair balance between career and family..I hope to have a business of my own in the future. I am ideally looking for a honest and good person with integrity.
I am currently visiting NY, USA but am not a paid member so </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>31, Groom, 5&apos; 7&quot; , Hindu: Khatri, Mumbai, IT Software</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=78f73d2f8140f6252032c20d683f5302i1336142&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I am truthful, . calm,  straightforward, confident and down to earth in nature who believes in the good qualities of a person. I am strictly non smoker and non drinker. I belong to Chandigarh. I am M.C.A and Microsoft Certified, working as a software engineer in Mumbai. Apart from my education I achie</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>30, Bride, 5&apos; 6&quot; , Hindu: Khatri, Delhi, Legal/ Law</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=ee7a4a610265e0cfbafb27d957ea7d18i669660&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> She is friendly, . soft-spoken and a very social person who gets along well with everyone. She is a very practical person with a decent sense of humor. She is the only child of her parents. Father is senior ranking tech. Executive in Navratna Central Public Sector Undertaking (CPSU), he has PhD from U</description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>