<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>FIND ELIGIBLE NRI SINGLES IN US...</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>44, Bride, 5&apos; 6&quot; , Hindu: Others, USA - New Jersey, Advtg/ Media/ Mktg/ MR</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=8c273d52d2586788ce5d94a409194f85i2948250&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I AM JUST. COMMING USA PRESENT WE ARE STAYING WITH MY BROTHER, AT ABSECON AND MY OTHER BROTHER AT CHICAGI IL,   Looking for: Very Co-Operative, Joint Family Nature, </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>29, Groom, 5&apos; 6&quot; , Hindu: Vaishya, USA - Kentucky, Student</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=06c794e238671ffac39b44b8dfc95dcfi2245044&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Doing Ph.D in. Mol.Science.in U.S.A.on Scholership.Will return to India after completion my study or after few years of service as the situation arise. At present I am only child of my parents- no siblings. Parents are residing in India and both are in service.I am soft, determined, like to travel, t</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>53, Bride, 5&apos; 0&quot; , Hindu: Vaishnav Vanik, USA - New Jersey, Banking/ Insurance</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=6ba28c0be0ae5910a097c81ee516f117i2109676&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I am simple. person. 
My Outdoor Activities:
Besides going to Gym (trade mill swimming toning muscles spa),  I regularly do Yoga and Meditation. I enjoy hiking, nature walk, feeding birds, sight seeing (Swiss, Hawaii, Bahamas.), watching movies (comedy, sentimental) and Broadway shows.
And Indoor </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>34, Groom, 6&apos; 1&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Kanyakubj, USA - Virginia, IT Software</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=f2c81cc263655daf0dcb83dcf0ab5095i2296429&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Down to earth, . intelligent, smart, caring and simple guy with lots of dreams and ambitions. His interests include traveling, working out, yoga, meditation, movies, reading books and playing tennis and cricket. He is very family oriented, cultural yet modern. Born in Indore, grew up in Dubai.
Fathe</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>36, Bride, 5&apos; 3&quot; , Hindu: Patel, USA - New Jersey, Medical/ Healthcare</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=faab775f0ad60b810cc1e70491f28a9ai1962846&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I would describe. myself as warm-hearted, cheerful, independent, spiritual, sensible, spontaneous, freedom loving and simple person but I can also be fun given the appropriate situation and company. 

I am looking for a life partner who shares common beliefs, values, views, goals and will be comple</description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>