<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>FIND ELIGIBLE NRI SINGLES IN UK</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>23, Bride, 5&apos; 4&quot; , Hindu: Scheduled Caste, , Student</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=be71ea5f5248164171bf684cd3866302i2848402&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Our daughter has. a very progressive and positive attitude towards life.she is fun loveing but a sincere and conscientious person.

Born in patiala, Punjab.

Lived in Mumbai/ Pune for last 18 years.

Schools;Bombay Scottish Mumbai and  St.Mary, Pune.

College:Sophia, Mumbai.

Did M.A.from Mum</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>24, Groom, 5&apos; 10&quot;, Sikh: Khatri, , Student</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=12b9079e0a28cc42943eb445b5224a1ci888704&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> hye this is. monti i live in london persuing DTI course from middlesex college which is located in oxford circus .my whole family live in INDIA i do work in gatwick airport doing dti course affiliate to atlantic airlines. we are three brothers elder brother is a doctor in india mid elder brother </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>24, Bride, 5&apos; 5&quot; , Hindu: Yadav, , Banking/ Insurance</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=5cdfb9bf262a3ef15179be40cb401006i2889104&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Educated at IIT. Delhi and working in a leading Investment Bank in London, Fun-loving, Aspire to have best things in life, Believe in relationship based on mutual respect, Looking for an open-minded Partner. Do not believe in caste system as prevalent in India.
Parents are based in Delhi. Father is </description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>23, Groom, 5&apos; 10&quot;, Hindu: Maratha, , IT Software</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=03d22d8c74df6fc39525599a1fd15fc7i1271960&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Good looking, loves. to perform the work in smart way. Pursuing my masters in Computers. Working at client side in UK at London for O2. Will stay in UK for next 1 year for a project and will be back offshore to work from pune location. Family stays in Mumbai. I am working with Tech Mahindra as a Soft</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>28, Bride, 5&apos; 2&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Audichya, , Accounts/ Tax/ CS/ Audit</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=61f396c9fd64ee2d90a5c4b2e8827f75i2560898&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I will be. bias to her as i am her best friend, but if you ask anyone she is always surrounded by, she has a personality which wins hearts, is warm and always charming, someone who you would want to run home too. She is smart, very well profound and has a great sense of humour. She has the smile that </description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>