<?xml version='1.0'?>
<rss version='2.0'>
<channel>
 <description></description>
<title>LOOKING FOR NRI GROOMS?????</title>
 <link>http://www.jeevansathi.com</link>
	<item>
 		<title>31, Groom, 5&apos; 8&quot; , Hindu: Marwari, , Accounts/ Tax/ CS/ Audit</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=4f1a993bdb45e00f163557d9b757e296i2943760&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> i am a. person with family values, like to live every moment of life. looking for someone special, work with United Nations in Geneva.  Looking for: understanding, with family values, good sense of humour, vivid, full of life, nature loving</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>33, Groom, 5&apos; 9&quot; , Hindu: Sindhi, , Entrepreneur/ Businessmen</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=8f2602a42cc871abba2e18ff7c54a095i1443901&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> I am a. very hardworking person and i live with my elder brother and his family here in Curacao, Netherland Antillies. I would like someone special who would love to live within a fun loving family. I have 2 elder brothers,  both married and both are working and living abroad. My late father was a ma</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>29, Groom, 5&apos; 5&quot; , Muslim: Sunni, , Advtg/ Media/ Mktg/ MR</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=016d4201d0a4673489d3b36d8979b4a5i2521455&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Hi, I am. IYAS. From Kerala, Working Dubai in a privet company.i will settled to india soon. I am a simple and broad minded man...MY PARTNER TO BE VERY NEAREST AND DEAREST TO ME, like a close friend....  Looking for: broadminded, undrestanding...etc.</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>29, Groom, 5&apos; 6&quot; , Hindu: Vaishya, USA - Kentucky, Student</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=06c794e238671ffac39b44b8dfc95dcfi2245044&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Doing Ph.D in. Mol.Science.in U.S.A.on Scholership.Will return to India after completion my study or after few years of service as the situation arise. At present I am only child of my parents- no siblings. Parents are residing in India and both are in service.I am soft, determined, like to travel, t</description>
 	</item>
	<item>
 		<title>34, Groom, 6&apos; 1&quot; , Hindu: Brahmin Kanyakubj, USA - Virginia, IT Software</title>
 		<link>http://www.jeevansathi.com/profile/viewprofile.php?profilechecksum=f2c81cc263655daf0dcb83dcf0ab5095i2296429&amp;source=RSS</link>
 		<description> Down to earth, . intelligent, smart, caring and simple guy with lots of dreams and ambitions. His interests include traveling, working out, yoga, meditation, movies, reading books and playing tennis and cricket. He is very family oriented, cultural yet modern. Born in Indore, grew up in Dubai.
Fathe</description>
 	</item>
</channel>
</rss>